[Music]
welcome everybody to episode 50 of
software engineering radio episode 50
this is a kind of birthday so we have 50
episodes behind us if we don't count
some of the administrative about and
announcement episode it's maybe only 48
but anyway 50 is quite something and
first of all I want to thank you all for
listening to SU radio we have gotten
quite a number of listeners I'm not
going to talk about the numbers because
it's always questionable how they how
these numbers are collected and whether
they are comparable but we're quite
happy with the number of subscriptions
of course there could be more and I'm
going to talk more about that later so
thank you all for listening for sticking
with se radio for giving us very
positive feedback after all the feedback
is what keeps us doing that what keeps
us running since there is obviously no
commercial interest in here it's the
positive feedback that keeps us going so
keep the positive feedback coming
however saying thank you is not the only
reason for this episode I want to talk
about two issues one is advertising and
public relations and the other one is
our website let's look at advertising
first now I'm not talking about
advertising on se radio rather what I
would like you to do is advertise for su
radio in your communities as I said we
have quite a substantial number of
listeners but we of course like to
increase that further not because there
is any financial reason again but rather
because we think that se radio is
interesting for more people than those
who know about it and currently listen
so to make it easier for you to help us
spread the word we have created a page
where you can get a number of logos
icons
also a poster that you can print on
paper and I don't know put it into your
office or into other blackboards or
something where other people can see it
so if you go to the SE radio net website
you will find at the top right on the
right side in our links section
relatively far at the top you'll find a
link under the heading of spread the
word where you can obviously click and
then download these advertising
materials so you can help us spread the
word and we would be really happy if you
did that at the other thing of course is
yet that you should go back to a podcast
le and vote for su radio it's quite
funny the first time I asked listeners
to do that we moved up quite a bit we
were ranked better than twit for those
of you who know twit you will agree that
that's quite something but this this
voting thing is reset every month so
you'd have to go back and vote for us
every month and yeah I think you you
could actually do this you can help us
be more prominent there so this is the
other way you can help us advertise now
let's get to the third topic I want to
quickly talk about third out of two I
guess and that would be our website the
website we have currently is not that
great it's just a default Lipson blog
page we can't we don't have a discussion
forum we can't easily tag episode so we
can have a multi-dimensional
categorization of our episodes so we
would like to have a better website a
real publishing content management
system I don't know like actually I
don't know very much about content
management systems and and that's why
we'd like to ask you the delusional
community to help us there so if you are
good at setting up content management
systems and organizing a community
website with with discussion forums and
and all that good stuff that we all know
from web 2.0 we would like you to help
us you might for example become part of
the SE radio team
playing the role of the webmaster you
could set up the system keep it running
and of course you'll be featured on the
website or for example if you have a web
publishing company if you do
commercially do a website development
you could give us a nice little website
with all these features for free and of
course you can have your logo on the
side and a big thank you note and we'll
of course mention you in every episode
in the thank you section at the end so
we're actually quite busy with producing
all the episodes so we probably won't
find the time to to do a decent website
in the next couple of months or even
even years so you see we have a very
long term vision for as you radio so
that's why we drawn on you the listeners
on the listener community to help us do
that so if you would like to help if you
would like to get more information
contact the team at team at se - radio
dotnet and to conclude this episode I'd
like to tease you a little bit and give
you some outlook on some of the episodes
we are going to have soon these days in
the next set of episodes we're going to
talk about design by contract about dsls
with Ruby about product line engineering
we've actually got two episodes and
product line engineering we have the
second episode on refactoring an
interview with Frank Bushman you
probably know him from the patterns
world we'll talk about safety critical
systems as well as compiler
metaprogramming we have a discussion
about devices and ubiquitous computing
we have a session about static code
analysis tools about their internals of
GCC we have a nice interview with
Kathleen Haney and Frank Bushman about
their new pose our foreign 5 book an
episode on small memory something about
so again so we have a lot of good stuff
coming we have a number of other
episodes in the pipeline so so keep on
listening and help us advertise I guess
that's that's it thanks again for
listening to AC radio to this this
episode number 50 we certainly have
enough
period for another 50 episodes and our
plan is to keep on going
thank you all and talk to you next time
bye
[Music]
thanks for listening to software
engineering radio if you want to get
more information about software
engineering radio or if you want to give
us feedback please go to our website at
se - radio dot net you can also contact
the team at team at SAE - radio dotnet
although we prefer entries in our
comment system on the website so other
people can see what you think
software engineering radio wants to
thank Henning poly for the intro and
outro music as well as Lipson for
providing the bandwidth this episode of
se radio as well as all other episodes
is licensed under Creative Commons
license
see the software engineer a do website
for details